http://www.speakupforachild.org/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
CASA of Tarrant County does not share, sell, nor lease your information to third parties. If CASA of Tarrant County receives your information you may receive mailings, information, and promotions from, or on behalf of, CASA of Tarrant County. If at any point you no longer would like to receive this information, please notify us of your wishes by sending us an email, mailing us a letter, or calling 817.877.5891.The Information We Collect The only time CASA of Tarrant County will ask for your personal information is when you register with us to make an online donation or register for an information session or other event. During this process, CASA of Tarrant County asks for your name, organization, address, city, state, zip code, phone, fax, email, gender and birth date.We will store that information in our database to add you to our mailing list so that we can send you information about CASA of Tarrant County.Typically the mailing list would be used initially for recruitment or fundraising events and programs that benefit and support the mission of CASA of Tarrant County. If you do not wish to receive such solicitations or notices, you will need to inform us separately that you do not wish to receive such information. In addition, if you contact CASA of Tarrant County, we may keep a record of that correspondence. If at any time, you no longer wish to receive e-mails from CASA of Tarrant County, please let us know.Our Commitment to Security CASA of Tarrant County operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our users.To protect your information off-line, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect from you online.Our Commitment to Children's Privacy Under the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, no web site operator is permitted to require a child under the age of 13 to disclose more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in an activity as a condition of participation.CASA of Tarrant County therefore does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from children under 13.Correcting Your Information If your personal information changes (such as your address) please contact us at 817.877.5891.Log Files To better understand our users, CASA of Tarrant County will review the server log files. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. Examples of such information include the URL of the Web page you were just on (known as the "Refer"), the IP (or Internet Protocol) address of the computer you are using, or the browser version you are using to access our site.Sharing On our site, you have the opportunity to make online financial contributions and to search for Volunteer and other Financial Donation opportunities. These opportunities are not hosted by CASA of Tarrant County. Therefore, the policies with respect to these areas differ from those applicable to our site.For information about our partners' privacy statements, Network For Good, VeriSign, Paypal, RallyUp and Race Roster for online donations, please see their associated web sites and privacy policies.Links Our website contains links to other organizations and corporations who support CASA of Tarrant County. We therefore encourage you to be aware and to read the privacy statements of each of these other websites. This privacy statement only applies to the CASA of Tarrant County web site.Contact Us If you have any questions about this Policy or want us to remove your personal information, please contact our web administrator.
